我今晚要在迪克家过夜
Hey, I'm sleeping at Deke's house tonight.
眨眼 眨眼 你懂的
Wink, wink, winky-wink.
迪克家 你是指他那个垃圾箱吗
Deke's house? You mean your boyfriend's dumpster?
是啊 所以我需要...
Yeah. So I need a, uh--
打破伤风疫苗吗
Tetanus shot?
还是提高择偶标准
Higher standards?
都不是 是要个套套
No, a condom.
我今晚要跟他做爱 我想要过程不舒服
I'm about to have sex, and I want it to feel bad.
我上次做爱后 我包里好像还有剩避孕套
I should have one in my purse from the last time I had sex.
你上次做爱时 世上就有包包了吗
They had purses the last time you had sex?
还没呢 我们用棍子绑住动物皮当包用
No, we carried animal hides tied with sticks.
没有这么久啦
It hasn't been that long.
这有一个 旁边还有《珍爱》的电影票存根
Oh, here's one next to this movie ticket stub from Precious.
好啦 是很久了
Okay, it's been that long.
你看《珍爱》的时候居然没戴套啊
You saw Precious without a condom?
上面写着"最佳使用日期为2012年9月前"
It says, "Best if used before september 2012."
就跟店里的牛奶一样
Just like the milk here.
真希望我有认识有带套套的男人
I wish I knew a guy with a condom.
男人 是男人就行
A man, any man.
奥列格 你身上有带...
Oleg, do you happen to have--
好 这些应该够你今晚用了
Okay, this should get you through the night.
但如果不够 可以用这个冷藏袋
But if it doesn't, you can use this freezer bag
然后用橡皮筋绑上
and a rubber band.
麦克斯 我把小杯子都摆好了
Max, I laid out the little cups,
你只需要把沙拉装进去就行了
so all you have to do is fill them with cole slaw.
这话居然从曾被福布斯评为
Said the girl who was on the Forbes
"值得关注的十大新星"的人口中说出
"Top ten to watch" list.
今晚我干不了这些杂活
I can't do my side work tonight.
通常我会说是因为太醉
Normally I'd say it's because I'm drunk,
但今晚是因为我又背痛又太醉
but tonight it's because my back hurts and I'm drunk.
宝贝 我有个能帮你
Here, babe, I got you something
减缓背部疼痛的东西
that might help your back feel better.
缩胸手术吗
A breast reduction?
别啊
No!
你为什么要糟蹋上帝的杰作呢
Why would you spit in the face of God?
大家冷静
Everybody, calm down.
这对胸器哪也不会去
Those aren't going anywhere.
如果它们真要走 我也会跟着它们走
And if they are, I am going with them.
我这有些退热贴可以让她舒缓肌肉酸痛
I got some cooling patches to soothe her muscles.
如果不管用
And when that doesn't work,
我有另一牌叫"哒嘛"的可以用
I have another brand called "Maui wowie."
上菜
Pickup.
-晚点见 爱你 -我也爱你
- I'll see you later. Love you. - Love you.
迪克 你嘴里那是什么味道
Deke, breath. What is that?
照烧牛肉干味 很难闻吗
Teriyaki beef jerky. Why, is it bad?
不会 再给我香一个
No. Give me another hit.
真好吃啊
That is delicious.
必须的
You know it.
麦克斯 既然你们认真要谈恋爱
Max, since you guys are getting serious,
干嘛不直接吃事前避孕药
why not go on the pill,
这样你就不用每晚都玩
so every night you won't have to play
"来找还有啥能当避孕套"的游戏了
"What can we turn into a condom?"
避孕药一个月分量的好像要50块
The pill is, like, 50 bucks a month.
那他妈的比养个娃还贵呢
That's more than it costs to raise a damn baby.
你的男朋友这么有钱 他付得起
Well, your boyfriend's rich. He can afford to pay for it.
我这下成了白人穷鬼无良妈了
Great, now I'm a white trash mom.
不要
Uh-uh, no way.
我要把迪克的钱留在更重要的事物上
I'm saving Deke's fortune for more important things,
像是多力多滋的辣味薯条
Like Doritos Dinamita.
那算是玉米饼界里的至尊了吧
Pretty much the filet mignon of corn chips.
我巴不得开始吃那个药呢
I mean, I'd be on the pill right now,
可惜现在唯一对我有兴趣的男人结婚了
but the one man interested in me is married,
所以我现在能吃上的只有苦药吧
so I guess that's more of a bitter pill.
-说认真的 麦克斯 考虑考虑 -好吧
- Seriously, Max. Think about it. - Fine.
为什么需要吃药的都不是男人
Why don't guys have to take the pill?
什么药都得是女人吃 避孕药 经痛药 迷奸药
We have to take all the pills. Birth control, midol, roofies...
你好 卡洛琳
Bonjour, Caroline.
尼可拉斯大厨 你来餐厅干嘛
Chef Nicolas. What are you doing in the diner?
天啊 我可不想被你看见我穿这制服
Oh, no, I never wanted you to see me wearing this.
所以麻烦你绅士点 往后退一步好吗
Yeah, so be a gentleman and take a step back,
因为这衣服不仅样子难看 味道更难闻
'cause as bad as it looks, it smells worse.
我觉得你看起来很美
I think you look beautiful.
你老婆看起来才美呢
Your wife looks beautiful.
行啊 姑娘 上
Oh, yeah. Get it, girl.
聊一会儿行吗 就在...
May I see you alone over there in the, uh...
某些人称之为"餐厅"的地方
I guess one would call it a restaurant?
就给你一分钟 我还在上班呢
But just for a minute. I'm working.
那是什么味道啊
What's that smell?
那是今日特别套餐 牛肉派
That's today's special. Beef pot pie.
但闻起来不像牛肉啊
Oh, it doesn't smell like beef.
因为不是牛肉做的
That's because it's not beef,
也不是今日做的 而且一点也不特别
It's not made today, and it's not special.
卡洛琳 你听我说
Listen, Caroline.
虽然我们的关系如同恋爱那般大起大落
We have all this relationship drama,
但我们根本没有在谈恋爱
and we're not even in a relationship.
我希望你能更深入地了解我
Please get to know me better.
来我家吃顿晚饭吧
Come to my home for dinner.
去你家吃晚饭 就我们俩吗
Dinner at your home, just you and me?
你觉得你老婆会怎么想呢
How do you think your wife would feel about that?
我跟她是开放式的关系
We have an open relationship.
你觉得我是那种
Did you think I'm the type of man
会偷偷跟其他女人做爱
who would have sex with another woman
而不先问过我老婆的人吗
without asking my wife?
美国人才那么搞好吗
That is so American.
-麦克斯 -你叫麦克斯干嘛
- Max? - Why are you calling Max?
我想确认一下我还没疯
I want to make sure I haven't lost my mind.
尼可拉斯说他跟他老婆说了我
Nicolas said he told his wife about me,
而他老婆同意我跟他上床
and she gave him permission for us to sleep together.
高招
Ha! Good one!
我以前打工的快餐店老板说 他老婆的遗愿
My boss at Quiznos once told me his wife's dying wish
是我让他用脸蹭我的胸
was that I let him motorboat me.
她可能被快餐店老板蹭过胸
Okay, so she may have been motorboated out of Quiznos.
但我不信你这套
But I am not falling for this.
我猜到你会不相信我了
Yes, I thought you wouldn't believe me,
所以我跟她约好周五你们两个视频聊天
So I set up a Skype call with her from France on Friday.
等等 你要我跟你老婆视频谈跟你上床的事吗
Wait, you want me to Skype with your wife about sex?
我现在是在访谈节目上吗
Am I on Dr. Phil?
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我买了件屌爆的新连衣裙
I got a new dress, and it's bitchin'.
快瞧瞧他
Hey, look at him. Oh.
没人告诉我菜单上新加了牛肉饼[猛男]啊
Nobody told me they added beefcake to the menu.
不好意思 菜单上猛男这道菜
Excuse me, beefcake has been on the menu
在我开始在这上班后就加上了
since I started working here.
终于啊
Finally...
餐厅里终于有跟我一样秀色可餐的人了
There's somebody in the diner as good-looking as me.
你好 我叫苏菲·科臣斯基
Hi, I'm Sophie Kuchenski.
尼可拉斯·圣克罗伊
Nicolas Saintcroix.
而且他还是法国人吗
And he's French too?
太棒了吧
Oh, come on!
抱歉 我刚才跟卡洛琳还没说完呢
I'm sorry, I was in the middle of a conversation with Caroline.
谁啊
Who?
我 那个脚正被你踩着的人
Me, the one whose feet you're standing on.
等等
Oh, wait a minute.
他就是那个已婚男人吗
Is this the married guy?
行啊 老妹
Oh, girl!
姐先让你两天 之后他就是我的囊中物了
I'm gonna give you two days' head start, and then he's mine!
你干嘛要在意她老婆觉得你头发如何啊
Why do you care what his wife thinks about your hair?
你又不是要跟她睡
You're not gonna be sleeping with her.
虽然说你跟她睡会更让你变得更有趣
Although you'd be a lot more interesting if you did.
我也不会跟他睡
I'm not gonna be sleeping with him either.
我希望我告诉他老婆这件事时 我能美美地说
And when I tell his wife that, I want to look good doing it.
我得比她好看两成
I have to look 20% better than her.
而人在视频上会丑个两成
And since Skype makes you look 20% worse,
所以我得比现在好看四成才行啊
I have to look 40% better than I do now.
你知道在发廊里跟我聊数学
You realize talking about math in a hair salon
是我最大的恶梦对吧
is my worst nightmare, right?
欢迎来到本发廊
Welcome to the Tristan Evans salon.
你好 我们是来做... 学生剪发的
Hi, hello. We're here for the... student haircut.
再说一遍
I'm sorry?
6块钱的穷人剪发
The $6 haircuts for poor people
让也还不是很会剪头发的人剪的那种
from the people who don't really know how to cut hair yet.
麦克斯 才不会呢 这发廊很出名呢
Max, that's not true. This is the Tristan Evans salon.
我相信会在这里学习的都是天才美发师
I'm sure that everyone that's enrolled here is a genius.
他们至少都是基男吧
At least tell me they're gay.
请你们到一旁就座
Just have a seat over there.
我会让美发学校部的人上来...
I'll have somebody come up from the hair school and-- shh!
小声点
So loud.
美发学校部 没问题
Hair school. Got it.
我们会乖乖坐在一边等他们
We'll just take a seat over there till they arrive.
妹儿 你就坐好 放轻松
Girl, you just sit there, relax,
让我杰米丝来把你的头发弄得超霸气
and let jameis make this head major.
真巧 我主修[霸气]的就是头呢
So weird, 'cause I majored in head.
妹儿 你真是伶牙俐齿
Girl, you are all everything.
水温有点冷
That's a little cold.
抱歉 你叫什么名字来着
I'm sorry, what was your name again?
丹
Dan.
丹 就丹一个字吗
Uh-huh. Dan? So just Dan?
不是什么丹妮还是丹翠儿之类的吗
You're not, like, a Danny or a Dantrell?
就丹
Dan.
我去拿点护发素
I need to get conditioner.
靠 麦克斯 我的美发师是直男
Damn it, Max, I got a straight one.
他哪里让你觉得他是直男了
What makes you think he's straight?
我都没准备好 他就一直把我的头"按下去"
He keeps pushing my head down before I'm ready.
水会太温吗
Is the water too warm?
为啥问 我裤子尿太湿了吗
Why? Are my pants too wet?
我真是爱死你了
Girl, are we in love?
麦克斯 把你的基男给我
Max, I need you to give me your gay.
你想得美
Yeah, right.
我把我左蛋蛋给你 也不给你我的基男
I'd give you my left nut before I give you my gay.
你本来都没想要弄头发
You weren't even gonna get your hair done.
但我一直想知道
Yeah, but I always wanted to know
被人上洗发水时
what it felt like to get a shampoo
不用被学校护士用细梳子梳头的感觉[头虱]
without a school nurse running that tiny comb through my hair.
丹
Dan?
我那边的杂志上有张
I have a magazine over there
时尚又有棱角的短头发型图
with a photo of a chic, piece-y, choppy bob.
-你能弄那个发型对吧 -没问题
- You can do that, right? - Sure.
简单 棱角短 没问题
Piece of bob. Got it.
-姑娘不错哦 -丹 丹
- 'sup? - Dan, Dan, Dan!
好 洗完了 可以剪了
Okay, done. You're ready to cut.
走吧 我可不想冒险让打折收费的直男剪头发
Let's go. I can't risk some discount hetero cutting my hair.
我们家里见吧 我都快要头发高潮了
I'll see you at home. I'm pretty close to a hairgasm.
这本来应该是我的福利
That should've been mine.
我都几年没有过头发高潮了
I haven't had a hairgasm in years.
她这几年什么高潮都没有过
She hasn't had any gasm in years.
天啊
Oh, my God!
麦克斯 这发型是你的新"避孕措施"吗
Max, is that hair your new form of birth control?
你看起来像是埃德娜夫人
You look like Dame Edna.
我就是照着她的发型做的
That's what I asked for!
泥嚎啊
Hellooo!
现在我的外表终于与内心一致了
Now my outside matches my inside
因为我的灵魂是个老年异装癖男
because I've always been an old drag queen
被困在一个年轻黑妞的身躯里
trapped inside the body of a young black girl.
泥嚎啊
Hellooo!
你好啊 麦克斯
Oh, hi, Max.
我以前也留过这发型
Oh, I used to wear my hair like that.
是为了方便夹带起司跟香烟进监狱里
I used it to smuggle cheese and cigarettes into the prison.
卡洛琳
Oh, hey, Caroline.
我就想确认一下
Just checking.
还是不要跟我要"睡"的
Still not sleeping with that French guy
那个法国佬上床吗
that I'm sleeping with?
就是不要 苏菲 他结婚了
Still not, Sophie. He's married.
那就好
Well, good.
因为我是来跟他老婆谈的
'cause I'm here to talk to that wife
人家的"洞洞"也要参赛
and throw my hoo-ha into the ring.
我还买了一个法式贝雷帽
I even bought myself a flat French hat
好让自己更有法国味
to make me more French.
另外 我买帽子的原因
Yeah, I got me the hat
是因为我不够时间留腋毛
'cause I didn't have time to grow out my pits.
电话一分钟后就来了 我就坐这里说吧
Okay, the call is in one minute. I'll just do it from here.
我本来还打算提着我LV的购物袋呢
I was planning to be holding my Louis Vuitton shopping bag,
但那只猫在里面拉了屎
but the cat took a dump in it.
麦克斯 把那台灯拿靠近我脸一点
And, Max, bring that lamp closer to my face,
这样视频上我不会看起来有八重下巴
So I don't have eight Skype chins.
行 但如果我太靠近灯泡
Fine, but if I get too close to the bulb,
我的头会爆炸
my hair might blow up.
她打来了
Here she is.
苏菲 慢走不送
Sophie, good-bye.
别想 我才不走呢 宝贝
Oh, no, I'm not leaving, baby.
那法国帅哥跟我是天造地设的一对
That French hottie and I are perfect for each other.
你瞧姐
I mean, look at me.
我戴着法式贝雷帽 包里还有法式长棍
I'm wearing a beret. I have a baguette.
贱人们 姐来啦
Bonjour, bitches!
深呼吸 然后别忘了 这事真是狗屁不通
Okay, take a deep breath, and remember, this is ridiculous.
你好 卡洛琳
Bonjour, Caroline.
你好 你是朱丽叶吧
Bonjour. You must be Juliette.
幸会幸会
It is nice to meet you.
我也是
And you as well, Juliette.
我想先跟你声明尼可拉斯与我的事
I just want to set the record straight about Nicolas and I.
我绝对不是那种...
I am not the type of--
可以 我同意你跟尼可拉斯上床
Yes, you have my permission to sleep with Nicolas.
再会
Au revoir.
就这样啊 她这就挂了
That's it? She's gone?
我没来得及用法语说"姐妹至上 男人滚蛋"
I didn't even get to say "hos before bros" in French.
人家还有很多话想说呢
So much more to say.
还有什么好说的啊
What more is there to say?
她都说我们可以跟他睡了
She said we could sleep with him.
不 我绝对不会跟尼可拉斯睡
No, I'm never sleeping with Nicolas,
他老婆说什么都没用
no matter what his wife says.
很好 因为你绝对不会跟人分享法国男人
Good, 'cause you could never share a French guy.
你连法式吐司都不愿意跟人分享
You won't even share your French toast.
谢谢你们陪我来
Thanks for coming.
我保证 在他家喝一杯就走
I promise, just one drink at Nicolas's,
然后我们一起去看电影
and then we'll go to the movies.
话说你居然真敢顶着这个发型出门
And, Max, I can't believe you went out with that hair in public.
我喜欢
I like it.
像我的艾斯特阿姨 只不过没她那么辣
You look like my Aunt Esther, but not as hot.
卡洛琳
Oh, Caroline.
你还邀请了迪克和...
I see you brought Deke and...
那位是麦克斯的母亲吗
Max's mother?
这发型和我妈的唯一共同点
The only thing this hair and my mother have in common is
就是吹"高"和嗑高[嗨]
they're both high.
尼可拉斯 我不会久留
Nicolas, I'm not staying.
我知道你为这顿晚餐费了很多心思
I know you went to a lot of trouble with dinner,
所以我也不想失礼
So I didn't want to be rude,
但我们喝一杯就要走了
but we can only stay for one drink.
天啊 你真漂亮
God, you look beautiful.
其实喝两杯也行
Maybe two drinks.
但绝对不留下来吃晚餐
But definitely no dinner.
我们本不该留下来吃的这顿饭真是美味
Well, that dinner we weren't staying for was delicious.
是啊 我们应该多多"不久留"
Yeah, we should not stay more often.
我喜欢你的小阁楼
I like your loft, man.
这地方超级适合
It's the perfect place to live
干一些激情四射的坏事
if you like to commit really sexy crimes.
我们该走了
Well, we should go.
别 你不留下来吃甜点了吗
No. You're not staying for dessert?
这真让我伤心
You're breaking my heart.
那就吃一块吧 我们可以分着吃
Well, maybe just one piece. We can share it.
我还以为你不喜欢跟人分享呢
I thought you didn't want to share.
他又没跟他的甜点结婚 麦克斯
He's not married to his dessert, Max,
而且只是吃一块而已
And it's just one piece.
我们来这的目的就是让他半点便宜都吃不着
We're here, so he doesn't get a piece.
你这个已婚单身男人一条龙服务得挺到位
You got a pretty sweet setup for a married man who's single.
奶油焦糖椰子蛋糕
Creme caramel au coconut cake.
不是软糖鲸鱼蛋糕啊
Well, it's no Fudgie the Whale.
多谢
Thanks.
我喜欢为朋友们做饭
I love to cook for friends.
尤其是漂亮的朋友
Beautiful friends.
尼可拉斯 就算你老婆同意我这么做
Nicolas, just because your wife gave me permission
也不意味着我会让你把我抱起来
does not mean I'm gonna let you take me over
扔到那张床单看起来很有档次的
to that king-size bed with
特大号双人床上
what looks like really good sheets
然后跟我疯狂做爱一整夜
and make love to me all night long.
直至早上也不停歇
and then again that morning.
你的背好点了吗 艾斯特
So how's your back, Esther?
莫蒂
Oh, Morty.
我有话要对你说
I have to tell you something.
你的心脏不行了吗
Is it your heart?
不是啦 是我在吃药
No, I'm on the pill.
我知道 你磕的药还不少呢
I know. You're on a lot of pills.
不是啦 是那个药
No, a pill-pill.
传说中的那个药吗
The pill-pill-pill?
是啊 你看
Yeah, see?
一弹开盖子 一颗药就会自动蹦出来
You just pop 'em out one at a time.
就像是给荡妇专用的糖豆
They're like pez for sluts.
说到荡妇
Speaking of sluts...
天啊 这场面太尴尬了
Oh, boy, this is awkward.
比我出庭作证指控自己半数家人还尴尬
And I've testified against half my family.
我同意 麦克斯
I agree, Max.
现在的场面是有点怪怪的
Things are a little uncomfortable.
所以我们何不让它变得更加奇怪呢
So why don't we just make this as weird as possible?
靠 我就知道他会杀我们灭口
Damn it, I knew he was gonna kill us.
有人会跳探戈吗
Tango, anyone?
老实说 我宁愿他杀了我们
Honestly, I prefer if you kill us.
好了 我们该走了 艾斯特
Okay, well, we gotta go, Esther.
不行 莫蒂 给我坐下来看戏
No, morty, sit down! I'm not missing the show.
这是餐后表演呢
It comes with dinner.
探戈 尼可拉斯 你在开玩笑吗
Tango? Nicolas, you cannot be serious.
你是不是不会跳舞啊 卡洛琳
Oh, maybe you cannot dance, Caroline?
怎么可能
Can't dance?
某年夏天 我曾教无家可归的青少年跳社交舞
One summer, I taught ballroom dance to homeless teens.
因为人在跳舞的时候 就不会觉得肚子饿吗
Because when you're dancing, you're not hungry?
快进快进
Fast-forward.
这是《亚当斯一家》里我最不喜欢的桥段
This is my least favorite part of the Addams Family.
-你瞧他的裤裆 -看见啦
- Look at his pants. - I know.
他的鸡鸡在裤裆的舞池里跟着起舞
That tango is giving him even less ball room.
留下来 我们不一定非要做爱
Stay. We don't have to have sex.
-可以吗 -我保证
- We don't? - I promise.
我要去洗手间一趟 麦克斯 你也是
I have to go to the restroom, Max. So do you.
进来 快进来 快进来
Come in, come in, come in, come in, come in.
可卡因在哪儿
Okay, where's the coke?
没有可卡因
There is no coke.
你没有可卡因 还把人叫进洗手间干屁啊
Why would you call anyone into a bathroom if you don't have coke?
真是太过分了
That's rude.
不是啦 我只是想跟你谈谈
No, I was just gonna talk to you.
那我绝对要来点可卡因才听得进去
Oh, then I'm definitely gonna need coke.
听着 你不能跟他滚床单
Okay, look. You are not sleeping with him.
当然不会
Of course not.
但今晚我觉得情况有些不一样
But tonight I'm thinking there's something special here.
我是说我们相谈甚欢
I mean, we talked, and we laughed.
你这是干嘛 "卡洛琳前情回顾"吗
What is this, "Previously on Caroline"?
如果你们俩扔下我 在里面嗑药
If you guys are doing blow in here without me,
我一定会非常生气的
I'm gonna be so pissed.
我倒想呢
I wish.
不是啦 卡洛琳想跟尼可拉斯滚床单
No, Caroline wants to have sex with Nicolas.
跳了那探戈之后还这么想吗
Even after that tango?
听着 现在我是想留下来过夜
Listen, now I'm thinking I want to sleep over,
但是绝不做爱
but not have sex.
所以是让他放进去但是不动的意思吗
Is that where he puts it in but doesn't move it around?
每次你醉得不省人事 我就会这样
That's what I do when you're passed out.
每次你醉得不省人事 我也会这样
绝不会有任何"东西"进"任何"地方"
Look, nothing is going in anywhere.
我只是想多了解他一些
I just want to get to know him better.
你真的觉得你可以跟他睡在同一张床上
You really think you can sleep in his bed with him
-却不把他的鸡鸡当抱枕吗 -当然
- and not use his penis as a body pillow? - Of course.
我跟上东区的每一个男生都试过
I've done that with every boy on the upper east side.
所以他们称我为"东区抱抱员"
That's why they called me the east side snuggler.
相信我
And trust me,
即使他老婆求我让我跟他做爱
even though his wife begged me to have sex with him,
但我也不会这么做
I'm not going to.
但你之前把我们拖来这的理由
But didn't you tell us the whole reason you dragged us here
不是因为你害怕跟他独处吗
was because you were afraid of being alone with him?
你这是干嘛 "卡洛琳前情回顾"吗
What is this, "Previously on Caroline"?
我懂你们的意思
Look, I get it.
如果你们俩真的觉得
And if you two really don't think I'm capable
我会把持不住的话
of not having sex with him,
那你们可以待到觉得我可以了再走
then hang out for a bit until you're sure that I'm fine.
可以 但我们不会在这耗一整晚的
Fine, but we are not staying all night.
麦克斯和迪克 这是给你们的毯子
Here are some blankets for you, Max and Deke.
你们可以睡沙发
You can take the couch.
我和卡洛琳睡床
Caroline and I will take the bed.
再次抱歉 是我们不好
Once again, our apologies.
我们醉得走不了
We are just too drunk to go.
真是太醉了
Too drunk!
你们俩才就分了一杯红酒
You did share that one glass of wine.
没错 我们都喝高了
Yup, we are too drunk.
所以醉到走不了路吗
So too drunk to walk?
我不知道 那你来判断下
Well, I don't know. You be the judge.
我对此感到非常抱歉
I am so sorry about this.
没关系 卡洛琳
It's fine, Caroline.
我知道这是怎么回事
I know what's going on here.
尼可拉斯 在你上床前
Oh, and, Nicolas, before you go,
我想再次感谢你今晚的美酒
I just wanted to say thanks again for the drinks,
晚餐
the dinner,
甜点
the dessert,
我的枕头
my pillow,
还有迪克的枕头
and Deke's pillow.
我们懂你意思了 老古董 晚安
We get it, grandma. Good night.
我们就睡在那边
We'll be right over there.
我就睡在这边
And I'll be right over here.
晚安 好好睡
Good night, sleep tight,
千万不要让臭虫"钻进"你的身子里
don't let the bedbugs have sex with you.
可是我会钻进你身子 对吧
Uh, you and I are gonna do it, right?
当然 我今早应该吃药了
Oh, yeah. Think I took my pill this morning.
不然就是我没吃
Either that or I didn't take my pill.
麦克斯 你今天有或没有吃药
Wow, Max, this is a big step
对我们的感情来说都算是垮了一大步呢
that you may or may not have taken today.
如果太麻烦的话
You know if it's too much trouble,
我们可以继续用避孕套啊
we don't have to go off condoms.
所以你就是当今世上那个
So you're the one guy in the world
唯一想戴避孕套的男人吗
who wants to still wear a condom?
你是不是有什么隐疾啊
Do you have something?
不 才没有呢
No, it's not like that.
我只是觉得开始吃药是个很大的承诺
I'm just saying the pill is a big commitment.
所以你不想进展到这一步吗
Oh, so do you not want to take this step?
因为我已经去过计划生育组织了
Because I already went to Planned Parenthood,
而我从未"计划"过任何事呢
and I never plan anything.
-麦克斯 我只是有点意外 -等下再说
- Max, I guess I'm just surprised-- - Hold that thought.
-怎么没有声音 -那又怎样
- I hear nothing. - So?
卡洛琳做爱的时候就是没有声音
So that's what Caroline sounds like during sex!
假装你在跟我说话
Keep talking like I'm here.
太爽了 宝贝
Ah, oh, yeah, baby!
那里 就是那里
Right there! That's the spot!
现在把我脸按上去吧
Yeah, now slap my face with 'em!
如果你在这 我就会说这种话啊
Well, if you were still here, that's what I'd be saying.
抱歉啦 我换一下
I'm sorry, I'll switch it up.
上吧 麦克斯
Uh, go fish, Max.
麦克斯 你在干什么
Max, what are you doing?
你们又在干什么
What are you doing?
我们没干嘛
We're fine.
我们只是躺着说话而已
We're just lying here talking.
其实不是 老娘已经欲火焚身了
No, we're not. I'm really turned on.
为什么 他对你做什么了
Why? What's he doing to you?
不是他 是我自己 我是肉食女
It's not him, it's me. I'm the predator here.
你说得对 你最好快阻止我
You were right. You better stop me.
上来跟我们一起睡
Get up here with us.
我才不要跟你同睡一张床
I'm not getting in bed with you.
麦克斯 你上床睡吧
Max, get in the bed.
我这人很知情识趣的
I know a jaques-block when I see one.
真是对不起
I am so sorry.
这样很蠢 我知道这对你来说太难[硬]了
This is silly. I know it must be hard for you.
现在不是了
Uh, not anymore.
昨晚当我们一起在床上时
You know, last night when you and I were in bed,
我意识到尼可拉斯可能就是那位
I realized I guess Nicolas is just gonna be one of
我人生中差点发生关系
those people in my life that I'm always gonna
但我又永远不会这么做的人之一
almost have sex with, but I never will.
你懂我意思吗
You know?
懂 就像我和你
Yeah, like me and you.
-你好 迪克 -你好 厄尔
- Hey, Deke. - Hey, Earl.
我今天最棒的谈话
Best conversation I had today.
麦克斯 昨晚我想你可能误会我
Max, last night I got the idea that maybe you thought
认为我不想让我们的关系更进一步
that I didn't want to take our relationship to the next level.
你这是干嘛 "迪克前情回顾"吗
What is this, "Previously on Deke"?
为了向你证明 我的确想跟你跟进一步
And just to prove that I do want to go to the next level,
我给你买了个环
I got you a ring.
天啊 麦克斯 真为你感到开心
Oh, my god, Max! I'm so happy for you!
虽然我一直以为我会是先订婚的那个
Even though I thought I'd be the first one to get engaged.
大家肯定都是这么认为的
I think we all thought that.
迪克 我不知道你要从口袋里掏出什么东西
Deke, I don't know what you're gonna pull out of your pocket,
但那最好是一把枪
but it better be a gun.
其实我知道你肯定不会想要那种指环
Actually, I know you don't want a ring-ring.
所以我送你一个阴道环
but how about a nuvaring?
阴道环
A nuvaring?
你怎么知道我里面大小
How did you know my size?
我迫不及待要戴进去了
I can't wait to try it on.
我可不会为你开个净身洗礼派对
Well, I am not throwing you a shower for that.
自从我目睹你第一天的药就貌似忘了吃
After I saw how you maybe forgot to take your pill on day one
结果隔天一整天乱吃药来确保安全后
and then took pills all day just to be safe,
我就想你可能需要点小帮助
I thought you'd need a little help.
所以麦克斯 你愿意跟我一起避孕吗
So there, Max. Will you not have children with me?
我当然愿意
You're damn right I won't.
慢着 这玩意戴上后还得过两天才管用
Oh, wait, I think these take a couple days to work.
我们今晚要去哪里弄避孕套呢
Where are we gonna get a condom for tonight?